Guide to the Steele Ranch Records, 1855-1973
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES A. CORRESPONDENCE: 1855-1973
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - 33. [1971], April 24.[Hillsborough, Ca.]. Betty Chadwick to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 34. 1971, April 29.Monterey, Ca. Dept. of Parks & Recreation (M.M.F.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 35. 1971, May 2.N.P. Randolph to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 36. 1971, May 12.Santa Cruz, Ca. Max W. Walden, Cooperhouse to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 37. 1971, May 23.Hartford, Conn. Wilfred to C.[B.]S., P.C.S.
    - 38. [1971], May 25.London, Eng. Fay to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 39. 1971, May 27.Jamestown, N.Y. Wilfred to C.[B.S.]., P.C.S.
    - 40. 1971, June 9.Salt Lake City, Utah. W[iflred] H.S. to C.[B.S.]., P.C.S.
    - 41. 1971, June 9.San Jose, Ca. W.[H.S.] to C.[B.S.] re: Steele genealogy., T.L.S.
    - 42. 1971, June 10.N.P. Pat Dutran to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 43. 1971, June 14.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy Harding to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 44. 1971, June 18.Stanford, Ca. Stanford Univ. (P.J.P.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 45. 1971, June 30.Oakland, Ca. Oakland, Museum (M.K.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 46. 1971, July 1.Same as # 45.
    - 47. 1971, July 4.San Jose, Ca. W[ilfred] H.S.[teele] to C.[B.S.]. re: genealogy., T.L.S.
    - 48. 1971, July 15.Oakland, Ca. Oakland Museum (L.R.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 49. 1971, July 20.San Jose, Ca. Wilfred [H. Steele] to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 50. 1971, Aug. 3.San Jose, Ca. W.[H.S.*] to C.[B.S.] re: genealogy., T.L.S.
    - 51. 1971, Aug. 20.San Jose, Ca. [W.H.S.*] to C.[B.S.]., T.L.
    - 52. 1971, Aug. 28.New Orleans, La. C. & Jack Stocker to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 53. 1971, Aug. 31.San Jose, Ca. W.[H.S.*] to C.[B.S.] re: early Steele family members., T.L.S.
    - 54. 1971, Sept. 3.N.P. Doris & Hank Sciaroni to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 55. 1971, Sept. 10.Stanford, Ca. Stanford University (J.P.B.) to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 56. 1971, Sept. 10.San Jose, Ca. W.[H.S.]* to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 57. 1971, Sept. 18.San Jose, Ca. W.[H.S.]* to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 58. 1971, Oct. 1.San Cerlos, Ca. Doris Sciaroni to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 59. 1971, Oct. 6.N.P. Marie Miller to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 60. 1971, Oct. 8.San Jose, Ca. [W.H.S.]* to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 61. 1971, Oct. 24.N.P. Ralph to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 62. 1971, Oct. 30.San Jose, Ca. W.[H.S.]* to C.[B.S.]. re: early Steele family members., T.L.S.
    - 63. 1971 Nov. 2.S.F., Ca. Wells Fargo Bank History Room (I.S.N.) to Mrs. W.[F.]S., T.L.S.
    - 64. 1971, Nov. 12.San Jose, Ca. W.[H.S.]* to C.[B.S.]. re: early Steele family members., T.L.S.
    - 65. 1971, Nov. 26.Houston, Texas. Corine [Wells] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 66. 1971, Dec. 1.Austin, Texas. Texas State Historical Assc. (J.B.F.) to Mildred Lee Damon., T.L.S.
    - 67. 1971, Dec. 5.Point Reyes St., Ca. Jack Mason to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 68. 1971, Dec. 8.Pescadero, Ca. Betty [Bradley] to [C.B.S.] re: sale of Green Oak Ranch., T.L.S.
    - 69. 1971, Dec. 9.Oakland, Ca. Oakland Museum (S.E.B.) to Mrs. W.R.S. [W.F.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 70. 1971, Dec. 10.Berkeley, Ca. Calif. Farm Bureau Fed. (A.G.) to Farm Bureau Member.
    - 71. 1971, Dec. 31.San Jose, Ca. W.[H.S.]* to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
  - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - 1. 1972, Jan. 4.Houston, Texas. Grace Wilcox to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 2. 1972, Jan. 9.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy [Harding] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 3. 1972, Jan. 12.[San Carlos, Ca.]. Hank Sciaroni to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 4. 1972, Jan. 13.[Davenport, La.]. Catherine B. Wilson to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 5. 1972, Jan. 28.N.P. Polly to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 6. 1972, Jan. 28.[Berkeley, Ca.]. Dorothy [Harding] to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 7. 1972, Feb. 4.N.P. Harold to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 8. 1972, Mar. 4.[S.F., Ca.]. Harold & Vi [Alvarez] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 9. 1972, Mar. 9.San Jose, Ca. Mayor Norman &. Mineta to Mrs. W.F.S., T.L.S.
    - 10. 1972, Mar. 11.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy [Harding] to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 11. 1972, May 14.[S.F., Ca.]. Harold [Alvarez] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 12. 1972, Mar. 17.N.P. Barbara Heacock to C.[B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 13. 1972, Mar. 18.N.P. Jack Mason to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 14. 1972, Mar. 21.Redwood City, Ca. Office of the [San Mateo] County Clerk. (R.B.) to C.B.S., T.L.S.
    - 15. 1972, May 5.Sacramento, Ca. Dairy Council of Calif. (N.M.) to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 16. 1972, June 19.Half Moon Bay, Ca. Agric. Extension Univ. of Calif., County of San Mateo (R.H.S.) to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 17. 1972, June 19.San Luis Obispo, Ca. San Luis Obispo County Historical Society (L.C.D.) to [C.B.]S., A.L.S.
    - 18. 1972, Aug. 1.Sacramento, Ca. Dairy Council of Calif. (N.M.) to [C.B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 19. 1972, Sept. 17.Santa Cruz, Ca. C.B.S. to Freda., A.L.S.
    - 20. 1972, Sept. 22.Fair Oaks, Ca. Neil McPherson to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 21. 1972, Sept. 26.Same as # 20.
    - 22. 1972, Oct. 9.Fair Oaks, Ca. Neil McPherson to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 23. 1972, Nov. 9.[S.F., Ca.]. Harold [Alvarez] to C.[B.S.]., A.L.S.
    - 24. 1972, Dec.[Salinas, Ca.]. Winona [Martella] to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 25. 1973, May 14.Berkeley, Ca. Dorothy Harding to C.[B.S.]., T.L.S.
    - 26. 1973, May 21.Fair Oaks, Ca. Neil McPherson to C.[B.]S., T.L.S.
    - 27. 1973, July 26.Rancho Del Oso, Davenport, Ca. Mrs. Charles A. McLean to M.D. Tarshes, County Manager, County of San Mateo re: present condition of Green Oaks Ranch house., T.L.
    - 28. 1973, Aug. 20.Redwood City, Ca. M.D. Tarshes to Mrs. Charles A. McLean., T.L.S.
  - Undated correspondence. (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous unidentified letter fragments. (Box 4, Folder 38)
- SERIES B. FINANCIAL PAPERS
  - Receipts: 1800's,Blinn. (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Bowen. (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Brown, Ella Steele. (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Brown, R. H. (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Brown & Bros. (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Captain Bunker. (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Clark & Coburn. (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Receipts: 1800's,John Connor. (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Elder. (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Eureka Dairy. (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Finney, S.J. (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Receipts: 1800's,GRAHAM RANCH (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Gushee, Horace. (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Gushee & Co. (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Gushee & Curtis. (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Gushee & Elder. (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Gushee & Son. (Box 5, Folder 55)
    Missing?
  - Receipts: 1800's,Hart, H.B. (Box 5, Folder 56)
    [UNK]
  - Receipts: 1800's,T.H. Hatch & Co. (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Jones, J.C. (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Captain Nelson. (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Parker, George. (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Schooner Sea Nymph. (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Scofield, R. (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Seely & Jameson. (Folder 62)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Sloop. (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Sloop Know Nothing. (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Steele. (Box 5, Folder 65-70)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Steele, E.W. (Box 5, Folder 71-74)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Steele, F.N. (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Steele, George. (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Steele, I.C. (Box 6, Folder 77-78)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Steele, O.N. (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Steele, R.E. (Box 6, Folder 80-81)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Steele, R.H. (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Steele & Co. (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Steele & St. John. (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Steele & Willson. (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Steele Bros. (Box 6, Folder 86-87)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Steele Bros. (Box 7, Folder 88-97)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Steele, Gushee & Co. (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Steeles, Gushee & Willson. (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Stevens. (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Thorton & Williams. (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Willson. (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Wilson, C.H. (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Receipts: 1800's,Unidentified. (Box 8, Folder 104-107)
  - Receipts: 1900, 1902-1904. (Box 9, Folder 108)
  - Receipts: 1905. (Box 9, Folder 109)
  - Receipts: 1906. (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Receipts: 1907-1909, 1911, 1915-1916, 1918-1919, 1921-1923. (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Receipts: 1926. (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Receipts: 1927-1929. (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Receipts: 1930-1931. (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - Receipts: 1932. (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - Receipts: 1933. (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - Receipts: 1934, January - June. (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Receipts: 1934, July - December. (Box 9, Folder 118)
  - Receipts: 1935, January - March. (Box 10, Folder 119)
  - Receipts: 1934, April - May. (Box 10, Folder 120)
  - Receipts: 1935, June. (Box 10, Folder 121)
  - Receipts: 1935, July. (Box 10, Folder 122)
  - Receipts: 1935, August - September. (Box 10, Folder 123)
  - Receipts: 1935, October - December. (Box 10, Folder 124)
  - Receipts: 1936, January - February. (Box 10, Folder 125)
  - Receipts: 1936, March - April. (Box 10, Folder 126)
  - Receipts: 1936, May 1 - May 10. (Box 10, Folder 127)
  - Receipts: 1936, May 11 - May 20. (Box 10, Folder 128)
  - Receipts: 1936, May 21 - May 25. (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - Receipts: 1936, May 26 - May 31. (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - Receipts: 1936, June 1 - June 4. (Box 11, Folder 131)
  - Receipts: 1936, June 5 - June 14. (Box 11, Folder 132)
  - Receipts: 1936, June 15 - June 22. (Box 11, Folder 133)
  - Receipts: 1936, June 23 - June 31. (Box 11, Folder 134)
  - Receipts: 1936, July. (Box 11, Folder 135)
  - Receipts: 1936, August. (Box 11, Folder 136)
  - Receipts: 1936, September. (Box 11, Folder 137)
  - Receipts: 1936, October - December. (Box 11, Folder 138)
  - Receipts: 1937, January - February. (Box 12, Folder 139)
  - Receipts: 1937, March - April. (Box 12, Folder 140)
  - Receipts: 1937, May. (Box 12, Folder 141)
  - Receipts: 1937, June 1 - June 10. (Box 12, Folder 142)
  - Receipts: 1937, June 11 - June 20. (Box 12, Folder 143)
  - Receipts: 1937, June 21 - June 31. (Box 12, Folder 144)
  - Receipts: 1937, July - August. (Box 12, Folder 145)
  - Receipts: 1937, September - October. (Box 12, Folder 146)
  - Receipts: 1937, November -December. (Box 12, Folder 147)
  - Receipts: 1938, January - February. (Box 13, Folder 148)
  - Receipts: 1938, March. (Box 13, Folder 149)
  - Receipts: 1938, April. (Box 13, Folder 150)
  - Receipts: 1938, May. (Box 13, Folder 151)
  - Receipts: 1938, June. (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Receipts: 1938, July - August. (Box 13, Folder 153)
  - Receipts: 1938, September - December. (Box 13, Folder 154)
  - Receipts: 1939, January - February. (Box 13, Folder 155)
  - Receipts: 1939, March - April. (Box 13, Folder 156)
  - Receipts: 1939, May. (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Receipts: 1939, June - August. (Box 14, Folder 158)
    there is no folder #159 [UNK]
  - Receipts: 1939, September - October. (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Receipts: 1939, November - December. (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Receipts: 1940, January - March. (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Receipts: 1940, April - May. (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Receipts: 1940, June. (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Receipts: 1940, July - August. (Box 15, Folder 165)
  - Receipts: 1940, September - December. (Box 15, Folder 166)
  - Receipts: 1941, January - March. (Box 15, Folder 167)
  - Receipts: 1941, April - June. (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Receipts: 1941, July - October. (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Receipts: 1941, November - December. (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Receipts: 1942, January - February. (Box 16, Folder 171)
  - Receipts: 1942, March - April. (Box 16, Folder 172)
  - Receipts: 1942, May- June. (Box 16, Folder 173)
  - Receipts: 1942, July - September. (Box 16, Folder 174)
  - Receipts: 1942, October - December. (Box 16, Folder 175)
  - Receipts: 1943, January - March. (Box 16, Folder 176)
  - Receipts: 1943, April - June. (Box 16, Folder 177)
  - Receipts: 1943, July - August. (Box 16, Folder 178)
  - Receipts: 1943, September - October. (Box 17, Folder 179)
  - Receipts: 1943, November - December. (Box 17, Folder 180)
  - Receipts: 1944, January - March. (Box 17, Folder 181)
  - Receipts: 1944, April - June. (Box 17, Folder 182)
  - Receipts: 1944, July - August. (Box 17, Folder 183)
  - Receipts: 1944, September - December. (Box 17, Folder 184)
  - Receipts: 1945, January - December. (Box 18, Folder 185)
  - Receipts: 1946, January - June. (Box 18, Folder 186)
  - Receipts: 1946, July - December. (Box 18, Folder 187)
  - Receipts: 1947, January - March. (Box 18, Folder 188)
  - Receipts: 1947, April - June. (Box 18, Folder 189)
  - Receipts: 1947, July - August. (Box 18, Folder 190)
  - Receipts: 1947, September - December. (Box 18, Folder 191)
  - Receipts: 1948, January - April. (Box 19, Folder 192)
  - Receipts: 1948, May - June. (Box 19, Folder 193)
  - Receipts: 1948, July - August. (Box 19, Folder 194)
  - Receipts: 1948, September. (Box 19, Folder 195)
  - Receipts: 1948, October. (Box 19, Folder 196)
  - Receipts: 1948, November - December. (Box 19, Folder 197)
  - Receipts: 1949, January - February. (Box 19, Folder 198)
  - Receipts: 1949, March - April. (Box 19, Folder 199)
  - Receipts: 1949, May - June. (Box 20, Folder 200)
  - Receipts: 1949, July - August. (Box 20, Folder 201)
  - Receipts: 1949, September. (Box 20, Folder 202)
  - Receipts: 1949, October. (Box 20, Folder 203)
  - Receipts: 1949, November - December. (Box 20, Folder 204)
  - Receipts: 1950, January - December. (Box 20, Folder 205)
  - Receipts: 1951, January - December. (Box 20, Folder 206)
  - Receipts: 1952, January - December. (Box 21, Folder 207)
  - Receipts: 1953, January - December. (Box 21, Folder 208)
  - Receipts: 1954-1955. (Box 21, Folder 209)
  - Receipts: 1956-1963, 1966. (Box 21, Folder 210)
  - Receipts: no date. (Box 21, Folder 211)
  - Receipts: no date. (Box 21, Folder 212)
  - Receipts: no date. (Box 22, Folder 213-216)
  - Bank Statements: 1922-1929 (Box 23)
  - Bank Statements: 1930-1933. (Box 24)
  - Bank Statements: 1934-1936. (Box 25)
  - Bank Statements: 1937-1939. (Box 26)
  - Bank Statements: 1940-1942. (Box 27)
  - Bank Statements: 1943-1946. (Box 28)
  - Bank Statements: 1947-1949. (Box 29)
  - Bank Statements: 1950-1951. (Box 30)
  - Bank Statements: 1952-1953. (Box 31)
  - Bank Statements: 1956-1960. (Box 32)
  - Check Stubs: 1869, 1871-1872. (Box 33, Folder 217)
  - Check Stubs: 1920-1929. (Box 33, Folder 218)
  - Check Stubs: 1930-1931, 1934-1939. (Box 33, Folder 219)
  - Check Stubs: 1940's. (Box 34, Folder 220-221)
  - Check Stubs: 1950-1952, 1957-1958. (Box 34, Folder 222)
  - Check Stubs: 1926-1946, 1949-1951. (Box 35)
  - Cancelled Checks: 1895-1899, 1902, 1905, 1926, 1930-1931, 1933-1934, 1947, 1949, 1952, 1960. (Box 36, Folder 223)
  - Deposit Slips: 1926, 1934-1936, 1938, 1942-1943, 1948-1950, 1952, 1956-1957, 1959. (Box 36, Folder 224)
  - Miscellaneous Bank Papers: 1903, 1935-1937, 1939-1942, 1944-1945, 1947-1952, 1956 and no date. (Box 36, Folder 225)
  - Ledgers: 1851-1854, 1857-1880. (Box 37)
  - Ledgers: 1869-1873, 1875, 1877-1881, 1894-1902. (Box 38)
  - Ledgers: 1873-1879, 1862-1864, 1866-1869. (Box 39)
  - Ledgers: 1874-1876, 1879-1881, 1894-1928, 1930-1935. (Box 40)
  - Ledgers: 1927-1944, 1946. (Box 41)
  - Miscellaneous Financial and Ranch Records. (Box 42, Folder 226-232)
- SERIES C. INSURANCE PAPERS
  - Insurance Policies: Fireman's Fund. (Box 43, Folder 233)
  - Insurance Policies: Fireman's Fund. (Box 43, Folder 234)
  - Insurance Policies: Inter-Insurance Bureau, Calif. State Automobile Assoc. (Box 43, Folder 235)
  - Insurance Policies: Inter-Insurance Bureau, Calif. State Automobile Assoc. (Box 43, Folder 236)
  - Insurance Policies: Miscellaneous. (Box 43, Folder 237)
  - Insurance Policies: North American Insurance Co. (Box 43, Folder 238)
  - Insurance Policies: Queen Insurance Co. (Box 44, Folder 239)
  - Insurance Policies: Queen Insurance Co. (Box 44, Folder 240)
  - Insurance Policies: State Compensation Insurance Fund. (Box 44, Folder 241)
  - Insurance Policies: Zurich Insurance. (Box 44, Folder 242)
  - Forms - Description of Payment: Farm Bureau Health Insurance Program. (Box 44, Folder 243)
  - Policy loan agreements. (Box 44, Folder 244)
  - Statements of earned premiums. (Box 44, Folder 245)
  - Miscellaneous insurance papers. (Box 44, Folder 246)
- SERIES D. LEGAL PAPERS
  - Affidavits - Occupational Classification. (Box 45, Folder 247)
  - Applications. (Box 45, Folder 248)
  - Boundary descriptions. (Box 45, Folder 249)
  - Claim for deferred classification - forms. (Box 45, Folder 250)
  - Contracts: 1935, 1937, 1940, 1942, 1944, 1940. (Box 45, Folder 251)
  - Court proceedings, transcripts. (Box 45, Folder 252-254)
  - Deeds: 1856, 1871-1873, 1875, 1879, 1896, 1904-1905, 1913, 1920, 1922. (Box 45, Folder 255)
  - Deeds: 1925, 1930-1931, 1934-1935, 1949-1950, 1961, 1965. (Box 46, Folder 256)
  - Deposit receipts. (Box 46, Folder 257)
  - Leases and agreements: 1841, 1957-1958, 1874, 1876, 1881, 1891, 1893, 1897, 1906, 1918, 1926, 1928, 1931-1932. (Box 46, Folder 258)
  - Leases and agreements: 1932, 1934-1936, 1939, 1941, 1943, 1945-1947, 1949, 1951, 1955. (Box 46, Folder 259)
  - Leases and agreements: 1956-1958, 1960-1961. (Box 46, Folder 260)
  - Leases and agreements: 1961-1963, 1971. (Box 46, Folder 261)
  - Leases and agreements: 1964-1966. (Box 46, Folder 262)
  - Matters of estate. (Box 46, Folder 263)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents and forms. (Box 46, Folder 264)
- SERIES E. PHOTOGRAPHS
  - Photographs: Steele, Clara and Emma. (Box 47, Folder 265)
  - Photographs: Steele, Clara. (Box 47, Folder 266)
  - Photographs: Steele, E.W.; Steele, Osman; Steele, R.E.; Steele, William F. (Box 47, Folder 267)
  - Photographs: Brown, Ella Steele. (Box 47, Folder 268)
  - Photographs: Steele, Emma and Chloe. (Box 47, Folder 269)
  - Photographs: Steele, Mr. & Mrs. I.C.; Steele, Frederick Nathaniel. (Box 47, Folder 270)
  - Photographs: Steele family members and friends. (Box 47, Folder 271)
  - Photographs: Steele family members and friends. (Box 47, Folder 272)
  - Photographs: Steele family members. (Box 47, Folder 273)
  - Photographs: Steele family members. (Box 47, Folder 274)
  - Photographs: Steele family members. (Box 47, Folder 275)
  - Photographs: Dairy cattle. (Box 48, Folder 276)
  - Photographs: Green Oaks Ranch. (Box 48, Folder 277)
  - Photographs: Green Oaks Ranch. (Box 48, Folder 278)
  - Photographs: Pacific coastside. (Box 48, Folder 279)
  - Photographs: Pescadero, Calif. (Box 48, Folder 280)
  - Photographs: Waddell pipe line. (Box 48, Folder 281)
  - Photographs: Pigeon Pt., Año Nuevo Beach, Waddell Beach. (Box 48, Folder 282)
  - Photographs: Pigeon Pt., Año Nuevo Beach, Waddell Beach. (Box 48, Folder 283)
  - Photographs: New Year's Creek [Año Nuevo Creek], Butano area, Bean Hollow, White House Canyon, Rancho del Osos. (Box 48, Folder 284)
  - Photographs: Miscellaneous. (Box 49, Folder 285-286)
  - Photographs: Worden family members. (Box 49, Folder 287-288)
  - Photographs: Miscellaneous. (Box 49, Folder 289-292)
  - Photographs: Unidentified. (Box 49, Folder 293-294)
  - Photographs: Unidentified and miscellaneous. (Box 50, Folder 295-301)
  - Photographs: Miscellaneous framed photographs. (Box 51-54)
  - Photographs: Miscellaneous photograph albums. (Box 55-56)
- SERIES F. MISCELLANEOUS
  - Calendars. (Box 57, Folder 302)
  - Envelopes. (Box 57, Folder 303)
  - Forms: registrations, applications, notices, etc. (Box 57, Folder 304)
  - Funeral attendance cards [1956]. (Box 57, Folder 305)
  - Genealogy. (Box 57, Folder 306)
  - Invitations and announcements. (Box 57, Folder 307)
  - Journals. (Box 57, Folder 308)
  - Lists, tables, and diagrams. (Box 58, Folder 309)
  - Memorabilia. (Box 58, Folder 310)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 58, Folder 311-313)
  - Permits and certificates. (Box 58, Folder 314-315)
  - Water usage records - notebooks. (Box 59, Folder 316)
  - Water usage records. (Box 59, Folder 317)
  - Water usage records - in order by user. (Box 59, Folder 318)
  - Water usage records. (Box 59, Folder 319)
  - Spiritualism. (Box 59, Folder 320)
- SERIES G. BOOKS & MAGAZINES
  - California, Public Works, Department of. Bulletin No. 5, Flow in California Streams. Calif. State Printing Office, Sacramento, Ca. 1923. (Box 60)
  - California, Water Resources, Department of. Bulletin No. 114, Directory of Water Service Agencies in California. June, 1962. (Box 60)
  - Cook book. [1800's].Handwritten. (Box 60)
  - Edwards, Rev. Justin, D.D. The Sabbath Manual; including The Sabbath a Family Institution. American Tract Society, New York. (Box 60)
  - Holy Bible. George E. Eyre and William Spottiswoode, printers. London. (Box 60)
  - Kelley, O.H. Origin and Progress of the Order of the Patrons of Husbandry in the United States; a History from 1866 to 1873. J.A. Wagenseller, Publisher, Philadelphia, Pa. 1875. (Box 60)
  - McLean, Alex. The Story of Rancho Del Oso. December, 1943. (Box 60)
  - Monree, John D. Chapters in the History of Delaware County New York. Delaware County Historical Association. 1949. (Box 60)
  - Orr, James L., compiler. The National Grange Choir. Executive Committee of the National Grange, Philadelphia. 1883. (Box 60)
  - Trident Water Meters. Neptune Meter Co. 1936 (Box 60)
  - United States, Interior, Department of. Second Report of the United States Entomological Commission for the Years 1878 and 1879 Relating to the Rocky Mountain Locust and the Western Cricket. Government Printing Office, Washington. 1880. (Box 60)
  - Wattles, Wm. C. Land Survey Description. Title Insurance and Trust Co., Los Angeles, Ca. 1956. (Box 60)
  - American Pipe Manual, eigth edition. 1930. (Box 61)
  - Mason Manual. Incomplete - some parts missing. (Box 61)
  - McLean, Hulda. The McLean Cookbook: Family Favorites. December 1963. (Box 61)
  - McLean, Hulda Hoover. The Book of Values. December, 1962. (Box 61)
  - McLean, Hulda Hoover. When I Was a Little Girl. 1966. (Box 61)
  - Music Books - two, incomplete - some parts missing. (Box 61)
  - Owen, David Dale. First Report of a Geological Reconnoissance of the Northern Counties of Arkansas, Made During the Years 1857 and 1858. Johnson & Yerkes, Little Rock. 1858. (Box 61)
  - Self-Contradictions of the Bible. Several pages of manuscript notes in beginning pages. (Box 61)
  - California, Water Resources, Department of. Bulletin No. 138, Coastal San Mateo County Investigation. March 1965. (Box 62)
  - Holy Bible. American Bible Society, New York. 1846. (Box 62)
  - Eikerenkotter, Edward A. List of the Names and Registrations of the Inhabitants of the County of San Mateo. Redwood City, Ca. 1886. (Box 63)
  - Fortune Magazine. Oct. 1932.Volume VI, Number 4. (Box 63)
  - Monteith, James. Comprehensive Geography. A.S. Barnes & Co., Publishers. (Box 63)
- SERIES H. MAPS
  - Maps - Steele Ranch area. (Box 64)
  - Maps - not pertaining to Steele Ranch area. (Box 65)
  - Maps - oversize maps.
- SERIES I. NEWSCLIPPINGS AND NEWSPAPERS
  - Newsclippings: Año Nuevo Island and Point (Box 66, Folder 321)
  - Newsclippings: Pescadero, Ca. (Box 66, Folder 322)
  - Newsclippings: Pigeon Point. (Box 66, Folder 323)
  - Newsclippings: Steele Ranch area. (Box 66, Folder 324)
  - Newsclippings: Steele Ranch - history. (Box 66, Folder 325)
  - Newsclippings: Issues of Seaside Reporter, local newspaper. (Box 66, Folder 326)
  - Newspapers - not pertaining to Steele Ranch and area. (Box 67-70)
- SERIES J. PAMPHLETS
  - Pamphlets: catalogs and informational pamphlets. (Box 71, Folder 327-329)
  - Pamphlets: guides to places of interest. (Box 71, Folder 330-331)
  - Pamphlets: miscellaneous pamphlets. (Box 71, Folder 332)